<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="shamian_name">Shamian</string>
    <string name="shamian_description">The island is a historical area that serves as a tranquil
        reminder of the colonial European period, with quiet pedestrian avenues flanked by trees
        and lined by historical buildings in various states of upkeep.</string>
    <string name="shamian_location">North Bank of Baie Bond, Liwan District, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="baiyun_name">Baiyun Mountain</string>
    <string name="baiyun_description">Baiyun Mountain covers a large area of northeast Guangzhou.
        It has been considered to be the top natural scenic part of the city since ancient times due
        to its magnificence and loftiness. The name Baiyun Mountain means White Cloud Mountain because
        the summit is wreathed in clouds whenever the sky clears after rain.</string>
    <string name="baiyun_location">Baiyun S Ave, Baiyun Diet Culture Gallery, Baiyun, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="yuexiu_name">Yuexiu Park</string>
    <string name="yuexiu_description">Yuexiu Hill once formed the northern end of the old walled city, though
        most of the walls have been dismantled and the city has now expanded far beyond it.</string>
    <string name="yuexiu_location">Yuexiu North, Yuexiu, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="nanyueking_name">Museum of the Nanyue King</string>
    <string name="nanyueking_description">The Museum of the Western Han Dynasty Mausoleum of the
        Nanyue King houses the 2,000-year-old tomb of the Nanyue King Zhao Mo in Guangzhou.
        Zhao Mo ruled from 137 BC to 122 BC, and his tomb was discovered in downtown Guangzhou in 1983.</string>
    <string name="nanyueking_location">Yuexiu, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="opera_name">Guangzhou Opera House</string>
    <string name="opera_description">Located downstream of the Pearl River, the opera house looks
        like two pebbles washed and smoothed by the river. The irregular-shaped buildings and the
        towers of Guangzhou CBD look like a fantasy landscape.</string>
    <string name="opera_location">1 Zhujiang W Rd, Tianhe District, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="financial_name">International Finance Center</string>
    <string name="financial_description">Guangzhou International Finance Center is the most modern
        area in Guangzhou. It gradually becomes the new center of Guangzhou. And many spectacular
        skyscrapers are built in this area.</string>
    <string name="financial_location">Tianhe, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="pearl_name">Pearl River Night View</string>
    <string name="pearl_description">Pearl River is the mother river of Guangzhou. The city was
        expanded rapidly along with the river. The night view of Pearl River is really great. You
    can walk on the river bank or have a boat trip here.</string>
    <string name="pearl_location">Pearl, Guangzhou</string>
</resources>