<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="shamian_name">Shamian</string>
    <string name="shamian_description">The island is a historical area that serves as a tranquil
        reminder of the colonial European period, with quiet pedestrian avenues flanked by trees
        and lined by historical buildings in various states of upkeep.</string>
    <string name="shamian_location">North Bank of Baie Bond, Liwan District, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="baiyun_name">Baiyun Mountain</string>
    <string name="baiyun_description">Baiyun Mountain covers a large area of northeast Guangzhou.
        It has been considered to be the top natural scenic part of the city since ancient times due
        to its magnificence and loftiness. The name Baiyun Mountain means White Cloud Mountain because
        the summit is wreathed in clouds whenever the sky clears after rain.</string>
    <string name="baiyun_location">Baiyun S Ave, Baiyun Diet Culture Gallery, Baiyun, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="yuexiu_name">Yuexiu Park</string>
    <string name="yuexiu_description">Yuexiu Hill once formed the northern end of the old walled city, though
        most of the walls have been dismantled and the city has now expanded far beyond it.</string>
    <string name="yuexiu_location">Yuexiu North, Yuexiu, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="nanyueking_name">Museum of the Nanyue King</string>
    <string name="nanyueking_description">The Museum of the Western Han Dynasty Mausoleum of the
        Nanyue King houses the 2,000-year-old tomb of the Nanyue King Zhao Mo in Guangzhou.
        Zhao Mo ruled from 137 BC to 122 BC, and his tomb was discovered in downtown Guangzhou in 1983.</string>
    <string name="nanyueking_location">Yuexiu, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="opera_name">Guangzhou Opera House</string>
    <string name="opera_description">Located downstream of the Pearl River, the opera house looks
        like two pebbles washed and smoothed by the river. The irregular-shaped buildings and the
        towers of Guangzhou CBD look like a fantasy landscape.</string>
    <string name="opera_location">1 Zhujiang W Rd, Tianhe District, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="financial_name">International Finance Center</string>
    <string name="financial_description">Guangzhou International Finance Center is the most modern
        area in Guangzhou. It gradually becomes the new center of Guangzhou. And many spectacular
        skyscrapers are built in this area.</string>
    <string name="financial_location">Tianhe, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="pearl_name">Pearl River Night View</string>
    <string name="pearl_description">Pearl River is the mother river of Guangzhou. The city was
        expanded rapidly along with the river. The night view of Pearl River is really great. You
    can walk on the river bank or have a boat trip here.</string>
    <string name="pearl_location">Pearl, Guangzhou</string>

    <string name="roll_name">Vermicelli Rolls</string>
    <string name="roll_description">A vermicelli roll is made from rice. Local chefs grind the rice
        into rice butter, then steam the rice butter into glittering and translucent pieces, which
        are then filled with pork, beef, shrimp, or other ingredients.</string>
    <string name="roll_location">Guangzhou Restaurant or Taotao Ju </string>

    <string name="wonton_name">Wonton Noodles</string>
    <string name="wonton_description">The wontons have a pork or shrimp stuffing that is wrapped in
        skins made of flour. The noodles are made only with egg and flour, and are squeezed with bamboo.
        The soup is cooked with pork bones or fish, but the detailed recipe is kept a secret by restaurants.</string>
    <string name="wonton_location">Zhuyuan Zhu Sheng Mian, Diyi Mian</string>

    <string name="tea_name">Chrysanthemum Tea</string>
    <string name="tea_description">Chrysanthemum tea is a flower-based infusion beverage made from
        chrysanthemum flowers of the species Chrysanthemum morifolium or Chrysanthemum indicum, which
        are most popular in East Asia, especially China. </string>
    <string name="tea_location">Everywhere</string>

    <string name="embroidery_name">Exquisite Embroidery</string>
    <string name="embroidery_description">The city stands close to the Pearl River Delta which gives its
        name to the local style of embroidery – one of the four most famous embroideries in China.
        First made during the Song dynasty (960-1280), Pearl River Delta embroidery combines texture
        and color with the most intricate stitch work. If you search hard, you might just find an
        extra special piece – one that is double-sided! The design on both sides is exactly the same,
        which is truly unbelievable! Designs usually portray birds, flowers, trees, and rivers.</string>
    <string name="embroidery_location">Most Shopping Malls</string>

    <string name="porcelain_name">Cantonese Porcelain</string>
    <string name="porcelain_description">Cantonese porcelain is the characteristic style of ceramic
        ware decorated in Guangzhou, the capital of Guangdong and (prior to 1842) the sole legal port
        for export of Chinese goods to Europe. As such, it was one of the major forms of exportware
        produced in China in the 18th and 20th centuries.</string>
    <string name="porcelain_location">Most Shopping Malls</string>

    <string name="tabNum">tabNum</string>
    <string name="tab0">Daytime Attractions</string>
    <string name="tab1">Night Sights</string>
    <string name="tab2">Foods</string>
    <string name="tab3">Souvenirs</string>

</resources>